{
    "subject": "resource/Claude_Crowl",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Gallipoli",
    "human_readable": "Claude Crowl died in Gallipoli.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9470204710960388,
            "question": "What happened to Claude Crowl in Gallipoli?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9190598130226135,
            "question": "Is there any information about Claude Crowl's life before his death in Gallipoli?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8365468382835388,
            "question": "Was Claude Crowl involved in a conflict in Gallipoli?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7874448895454407,
            "question": "Where did Claude Crowl die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5895859599113464,
            "question": "Who was Claude Crowl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.560032844543457,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Claude Crowl's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44616377353668213,
            "question": "Was Claude Crowl a soldier?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3187538981437683,
            "question": "What time period did Claude Crowl live in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23344825208187103,
            "question": "Are there any historical records about Claude Crowl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18809543550014496,
            "question": "What is the significance of Gallipoli?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Claude Crowl died in Gallipoli.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2980_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical records about Claude Crowl?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2980_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What time period did Claude Crowl live in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2980_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Claude Crowl a soldier?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2980_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2980_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2980_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2980_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2980_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2980_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2980_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2980_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2980_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2980_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2980_54.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the documents, I found that:\n\n* Private Claude Terrell Crowl was indeed killed in action whilst landing at Gallipoli on 25 April 1915 (document 1 and document 4).\n* His cousin Captain Joseph Terrell Crowl was also killed at Gallipoli on Walters Ridge on 27 June 1915, aged 31 (documents 2, 4, and 6).\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\nResponse: {'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Claude Crowl died in Gallipoli.\" Specifically, multiple sources mention his death at Gallipoli on April 25, 1915."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}